<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>English Posts on DaoyuanWu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English Posts on DaoyuanWu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:44:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning for beginners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/2024/07/05/ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:44:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/2024/07/05/ml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Machine Learning is the subfield of the artificial interlligence that give computers the ability to learn without being explicityly programmed.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main types of machine learning are &lt;strong&gt;supervised learning&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;unsupervised learning&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;supervised-learning&#34;&gt;Supervised Learning&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supervised Learning&lt;/strong&gt; learns from being given “right answers” has been used most widely in real-world applications including &lt;em&gt;spam filtering, speech recoginition, machine translation, online adversising, self-driving cars and visual inspection&lt;/em&gt;. The two major algorithms in supervised learning are &lt;strong&gt;regression&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;classification&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlight of Calculus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/2024/06/25/highlight-calc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:32:25 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/2024/06/25/highlight-calc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;highlight-of-calculus&#34;&gt;Highlight of Calculus&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These notes capture the key highlights and concepts from the renowned MIT calculus course taught by Professor Gilbert Strang. I wrote it mainly out of the motivation to active recall the knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt. If it could also help someone to understand the calculus, that would be much greater!
Faymen said the expert could teach the conception so simple that even a child can understand without problmes. If you find there are something unclear, confusing or mistakes. Please leave me the comment below or contact me via email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
